[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Welcome back, Gabo.
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
You thought I was going
to forget about it?
I got imprisoned for eight
years because of you!
You'll pay for all of it!
- [GRUNTING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
Django was beaten
to a pulp by Gabo!
That means, Gabo is the new
king of Ginintuang Lupa!
This won't be the last
you'll see me, Gabo.
To the new king!
- Long live Gabo!
- Long live!
I'll send you to your grave!
You promised you'd change
for the better, didn't you?!
What if they killed you?!
I promised myself
that when I get out,
I'll make him feel all
the suffering I went through!
Don't waste your time
getting revenge
at those
good-for-nothing pricks!
Listen to me. I just want
you to have a decent life.
I'm sorry for letting my
emotions get the best of me.
I promise I'll try my best
to change.
I'll avoid getting
into any trouble.
Your Aunt Pinky has this piece
of property she's selling.
We bought it.
It's in Ginintuang Lupa.
But there are many families
living there.
And that area's known
for crime.
They'll just move
to the hills or somewhere.
They always find
a place to stay.
But, Mom, we can't just
let them be.
Many families
will be left homeless.
Let's put it this way.
They've been staying at
Ginintuang Lupa for years.
So, as the new owners,
it's our turn to make use
of that property.
I told Papa during our talk
that I'll turn over a new leaf.
So tomorrow,
I'll look for a job.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
I'm glad that you and Gabo
had a serious talk.
I really hope
he fulfills his promise.
Well, I know that Gabo
has a good heart.
It's just that he grew up
in a tough environment.
We can't change that now.
People here are taught that
if you don't fight back,
you'll be
at a disadvantage.
I really hope he changes
for the better.
He'll end up living
a messy life
if he keeps getting
into trouble.
Why don't we just
let him be?
He was imprisoned
for eight years.
Maybe he learned
something there.
I mean, he wouldn't be
released on parole
if he hadn't done something
good there.
That's right.
You know, I'm proud
of my son.
He can just be short-tempered
sometimes.
Maybe once he has a
family and job...
he'll change.
I guess when he gets older...
he'll realize the things he
needs to change.
I hope so. I really do.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Morning! Excuse me.
I'm coming through.
Move. Make some way.
Good morning!
[TEKLA] Hey.
- Mister Elton.
- Oh. Tekla.
- Wow! Nice outfits.
- I know, right? How do we look?
You're really serious
about looking for a job.
- Finally tired of being bums?
- You're so harsh.
Well, it's high time
you help your parents out
and stop loafing around
in the streets.
I hate his tone!
That's why we're going
job hunting with Gabo.
Look, job hunting is easy.
The question is
whether we'll be hired.
I mean, look at us.
We didn't even finish
elementary school.
[TEKLA LAUGHING]
Well, excuse me, Bong.
Don't lump me in with you.
Because look at me.
With how pretty and sexy I am,
you think no one
would hire me?
I'm sure you'll be hired.
- With your beauty...
- Oh, thank you.
- and your fair skin...
- Right?
- Try a beerhouse.
- [BONG, IPE CACKLING]
- Like your grandmother.
- You're so mean!
I have bigger dreams, you know!
And with this beautiful face?
I should be working
at a hotel or an office! Right?
Wait, do you even know
how to speak English?
Nope!
But that doesn't matter.
It's all about looks nowadays.
- She has a point.
- Hmph! They're such killjoys.
- [DANTE LAUGHING]
- Bye, Mister Dante!
[TEKLA] Anyone home?
- Come in!
- Good morning!
- Hey!
- Where's Gabo?
- Join us for breakfast.
- Breakfast?
- Yes! Join us.
- Perfect! We haven't eaten.
- [BETCHAY CHUCKLES]
- Wow.
That looks delicious!
But it's only for us.
Oh, come on.
They're going job hunting.
Of course, they'll need energy.
So, they have to eat.
Miss Mameng is right,
Miss Betchay.
Just get one, okay?
- Okay.
- Thanks.
You know what? I'm on a diet.
Just take my share.
- You're such a killjoy.
- What?
But don't worry.
Everything you gave us?
Put it all on our tab.
We'll pay for it once we receive
our first salaries.
I hope so!
- Where is Gabo?
- [BETCHAY] Oh.
[THRILLING ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
If I get heads,
I'll surely get a job.
But if I get tails, that means
I'm down on my luck.
[THRILLING ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ooh! Heads!
It means I'm going
to land a job. [CHUCKLES]
[SMOOCHES]
Looks like it's my lucky day.
[BETCHAY] Gabo!
- Wow! So handsome!
- Look at you!
- [LAUGHTER]
- We're job hunting, right?
You look like you're auditioning
for reality TV!
[RUDY]
Son, sit down and eat first.
- [MAMENG] Yeah.
- Thanks, Pa.
But we have to go.
We need to be early
to beat all other job hunters.
[MAMENG] Okay.
But, Gabo...
Don't forget what you
and father talked about.
And I hope this marks the start
of you reaching your dreams.
[BETCHAY] Of course!
He's going to reach
all of his dreams
as long as he works hard
and follows the right path.
Pa, we'll get going now.
- Take care.
- Bye, auntie.
- Be safe, okay?
- Excuse us.
- Good luck!
- Thank you!
- We'll be off now.
- Bye, Miss Mameng.
- Bye-bye!
- Take care!
- Come on. Betchay.
- [IPE] Thank you!
The kid's trying to change.
When will you?
- Huh?
- Excuse me.
Gabo! Gabo?
Gabo! Gabo! Gabo!
- Gabo!
- Pa?
Uh...
I really do hope you land a job
so you can truly change
for the better.
Don't worry, Pa.
I promise you we'll
come back here with jobs.
Office workers, perhaps?
- [LAUGHTER]
- I'll count on that!
I mean, look at you!
You all look like you're
going to the office!
- Or the bank!
- Yeah!
- More like bank robbers!
- [LAUGHTER]
Don't worry, Mister Rudy.
We got you.
Once we get our pay, we'll treat
you to a boodle fight!
Oh, I hope you make good
on your promise!
- Yeah.
- Go on now.
- Be careful.
- We'll get going now.
Take care, son.
- Bye, Mister Dante.
- Bye.
- Thanks, Mister Rudy.
- Mister Dante, don't jinx us!
- Let's go.
- Come on!
[ISOBEL SIGHS]
I can already picture
the sparkling new...
...Ginintuang Lupa Beach Resort
Casino Hotel!
After that, I'll buy you
all the cars you want.
Oh, you know, I have
this special car in mind.
Which one?
I want one with
the matching umbrella!
I know a contractor who has one.
Uh, boss? The cars are ready.
- Let's go.
- [ISOBEL] Oh, yes. Okay! Go!
- Good morning, ma'am.
- Good morning.
- Good morning...
- Hi, good morning!
...my beautiful baby!
Leaving already?
Well, the investors
changed their minds.
They want to see
the property today.
So, you'll be needing an escort?
- No, we can manage.
- [MAX] Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Did you guys talk about
where the people
from Ginintuang Lupa
are going to move?
We don't need to discuss it.
Just do your job.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Take care.
- Bye, Mom.
- Yeah.
[BONG] Gabo, what kind of job
are we getting?
Whatever. Anything.
Hey!
We can work at a call center!
Isn't that the trend now?
Us?! At a call center?!
You doubting us?
We can speak English, right?
[BONG] Yes, of course!
The problem isn't English.
The problem is,
how far did we get in school?
Exactly. As far as I know,
we need a college degree.
- Is that so?
- You probably forgot.
We only reached third grade.
Whoa, hold on! That's just you
three. Don't include me.
Excuse me.
I finished fifth grade.
- Hello?
- [LAUGHS] Look at this girl.
Flexing like she's all that.
Oh! This is perfect!
"Wanted: live seller"!
What's a live seller?
People who sell stuff
on their phones.
You know, online.
Yeah, Gabo. We've seen those.
They're the hot, sexy girls.
- Mm.
- So? Let's go for it!
Come on, hurry!
Hello, madam!
- Hey! You look great in pink!
- Good day to you!
What can I do for you?
Uh, we'd like to apply
for a job.
Oh, we don't have openings
for repackers anymore.
You're so funny, madam!
Look at me. Do I look like
a repacker to you?
Of course, we're applying
to be live sellers.
You guys? Live selling?
Do you even know
how to sell?
- Ah...
- [IPE] Ah...
- Yes, yes, yes!
- We know how.
Yes! We do, madam!
You know what,
just let us try it out
so you can see
how good we are.
Alright, fine.
I'll give you a shot.
If you sell a lot today,
you're hired.
Oh, madam, don't worry.
We got this. We'll sell out
your stock today.
Hello! Hello! Hello!
Good day to everyone!
I'm Tekla, the prettiest
live seller on Earth!
And we are here at the most
beautiful hardware store
in the whole Philippines!
And the first thing we have
for you are nails! Whoo!
These nails are so strong.
Stronger than relationships!
So buy them now!
They can handle any disaster.
They're stainless.
They won't rust
through storms, floods,
earthquakes, anything!
Your grandkids will use them!
They're really that good!
- So buy them now!
- Why is she like that?!
Seriously!
- Like she doesn't know how!
- Great deal right here!
The viewers don't look happy.
Oh, I'm not for sale, sorry--
Hey! What is this!
I thought you knew how?
We're just warming up.
Look, people are buying.
- You'll ruin my business!
- We're just getting started.
Maybe they want the drill.
- Yeah, let's do that.
- Maybe they haven't seen this.
This is a drill! Yes! For all...
of our friends out there,
this is a top-quality drill.
- Are they doing this right?
- [BONG] It's a tool
made to punch holes, perfect
for your no-good neighbors.
- Look at that.
- Anyone who wants to buy,
just comment "mine."
It's cheap and durable,
but they don't seem to want it.
Ipe, Ipe, you're up.
- Oh no, it's his turn now.
- This one...
is a hacksaw. It cuts anything.
It can cut...
steel, sheet metal, wood,
even your water line.
Huh? What do you mean ugly?!
- Gabo, your turn.
- [BONG] You can do it.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Can he make a sale?
- Hello, viewers!
Come buy!
We have a hammer for sale!
It's tough enough
to smash your heads!
- [TEKLA] That's right!
- Comment "mine" now!
This steel won't rust, even
if I smash it in your face.
- [LAUGHING]
- We'll lose money here.
This is the worst.
What? We look like thugs?
- Oh boy.
- [TEKLA GASPS]
- These viewers are crazy.
- You guys are too much!
If you want, come down here!
You sell, and I'll break
your head!
- Come here! You're so smug!
- What?! Huh?!
- They don't know us!
- You're watching us,
but you can't afford anything!
You're so cocky just
because you're watching!
- Tough guys behind a screen!
- Come over here!
I'll smash your face!
- Huh?! Huh?!
- [OBJECTS CLATTERING]
- [WOMAN] Hoy, stop it!
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- Why did it end up like this?!
- Stop!
- You'll ruin our business!
- What are you doing?!
Get out of here!
We're calling the cops!
- Gabo, run!
- Don't ever show your faces!
- You guys are crazy!
- All of you, get out!
[SEBASTIAN] Sam.
We checked out the jewelry
stores in Chinatown.
Some of them are selling
their goods at very low prices.
They're also supplying
online sellers.
These shops are owned by a
foreign national named Mr. Chan.
Mr. Chan?
Ma'am, check this out.
We did a background check
on Mr. Chan.
He's a foreign national.
He's faced tax evasion
charges before,
but he always gets away with it.
Oh no.
Looks like someone in the
government is backing him up.
Okay. Let's keep an eye
on Mr. Chan.
Find every information
you can get on him.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Let's go, boys.
- Let's go.
[IPE] Miss Betchay is right.
We'll have a hard time
finding work
because we didn't finish school.
[TEKLA SIGHS DEEPLY]
I don't get it. We all have
pleasing personalities.
What pleasing personality
are you talking about?
Didn't you just destroy
the live selling studio
that's why we got fired?!
Gabo, what do we do now?
Should we just give up
on the job hunt?
What do you think, Gabo?
Should we keep going?
Of course.
Why give up now?
I'm sure we can find plenty
of work here at the market.
Miss Betchay's right again.
We'd really end up
working at the market.
Don't be picky.
What's important is that we find
decent jobs.
Come on.
Let's keep looking.
We could've profited
off my beauty earlier,
but you just had
to get us all fired!
Over there!
- They're hiring!
- "WANTED: DELIVERY MEN..."
- Huh?
- Let's go!
See there?
They're hiring delivery men
and a cashier.
Perfect!
- Tekla.
- Yeah?
Being a cashier would suit you.
You're such a slave for money.
[MOCKING LAUGH]
You think you're funny?
With you, the store might end up
with more losses than gains.
Why?
Well, we all know
you have sticky fingers.
Excuse me?! For your
information, I've changed!
I only steal money
from my grandma nowadays.
Excuse me.
- Yes?
- We're here to inquire...
...if you're still looking
for delivery men and cashiers.
Yes, why? You interested?
- [BONG] Yes.
- Well... yes.
We're hoping to find
decent jobs, sir.
We can do whatever you ask us.
Okay, I have goods scheduled
to be delivered later.
[TEKLA SQUEALS] Perfect!
How about a cashier?
Have you found one yet?
Ah. [CHUCKLES]
You're perfect for the job.
- [TEKLA GIGGLES]
- You'll surely attract buyers!
You're right, sir.
You have a good eye.
Alright, come on in.
I'll give you an orientation.
- Right now?!
- Let's go!
- Orientation?
- I like it here already!
[TEKLA] We're so lucky!
This is where I stack
the bags of garlic and onions.
Later, you'll deliver them
to resellers
and our partner restaurants.
You think you can do it?
Of course, boss.
That's easy.
[IPE] Piece of cake, boss.
- Basic!
- [LAUGHTER]
[BONG] Basic, indeed.
But how much
are we going to make?
Six hundred per day.
- Alright.
- Wait, boss.
What about me? How much
am I going to make?
You should pay me more.
I'll be handling your money.
With your beauty,
you deserve 800 a day.
- [SQUEALS] Sounds good to me!
- That's a lot!
Okay, you can start.
For now, organize those sacks.
Later, I'll have you
deliver them.
Okay.
As for you, dear,
I'll show you the counter.
- Let's go.
- This way.
Let's get started.
- You see these?
- Yes, sir.
Make sure these are correct.
Excuse me, here's your order.
[VENDOR] Put them down.
[IPE] Should we put them inside?
Here you go.
[BONG] Make way!
Coming through!
Excuse me, sir.
Here's your order.
[GRUNTS]
- There's the garlic.
- And the onions.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
Looks like you're
all hardworkers.
Oh, of course, boss.
You know, we've been looking
for jobs all day.
Good thing you were hiring.
As long as you work hard,
we won't have any problems.
Especially you.
- Do you have a boyfriend?
- [CHUCKLES]
I do.
I already have a boyfriend.
It's Gabo, one of the
workers you hired.
If you haven't heard,
he just got out of jail.
He served eight years.
You see, the last time someone
tried to take advantage of me,
he ended up with murder charges.
[NERVOUS CHUCKLE]
O-Okay, just make sure
everything's in order.
- Check our balances.
- Sure thing.
See if everything's
accounted for, okay?
You can count on me.
[COMICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
What a dirty old geezer.
I'm already taken. [CHUCKLES]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[WOMAN] I'll buy one half kilo.
How much is it?
Psst.
[WOMAN] Here's my payment.
Tolits will approach that
woman with money.
Miss, have it weighed again
just to make sure.
There are vendors here
who scam buyers.
Check the scale carefully.
It's all good, right?
Alright then.
- Hey! That's my wallet!
- Huh?
- Thief!
- Go, go, go!
- Run!
- Help! Thief!
[WOMAN] Thief! Thief!
Move! Out of the way!
Ow!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey!
- Ow!
- Ow! Stupid!
- Gabo! Gabo!
- Get up!
What did you do
this time?
- Nothing.
- We didn't do anything.
[GABO] Miss, what happened?
They took my wallet.
You're stealing from people here
at the market now, huh?
- Have you no shame?
- Who took it?
- I don't have it. I swear.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- Ow!
- I don't have it, Gabo.
- Now, you.
- Who took it?
- I didn't steal anything.
- [BLOW LANDS]
[IPE] Come on, stop lying.
Who took it?
You still won't tell the truth?
We didn't steal anything,
Gabo.
- We didn't-- Ow!
- [BLOW LANDS]
We didn't steal anything, Gabo.
That woman is lying.
You wont fess up, huh?!
Gabo, no.
Gabo.
You choose. Get beaten up
or tell the truth?
I don't have it, Gabo.
- Is that so?
- Gabo!
Fine, then!
- Hit him.
- Good idea.
- Hit him!
- Go!
[GABO] Hit him or
I'll destroy your face.
- [GABO] I said hit him!
- [IPE] Go.
Do it or I'll hit you
myself.
- Alright.
- Hit him.
I'm sorry, Binoy.
Let's just do this.
I can't have Gabo
punch me.
- Just not too hard, okay?
- Yeah.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [CROWD CHEERING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[TOLITS] Come on, let's go.
We're done, right, Gabo?
You still won't tell
the truth?
- Who took the wallet?
- I don't have it, Gabo.
- Just tell the truth.
- Who took it?!
- Hit him.
- Huh?
- Hit him!
- [IPE] Do it.
I have to do this
or Gabo will hit me.
- Alright.
- I'll put force on it, okay?
That's what Daboy
did earlier.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [CROWD CHEERING]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[TOLITS] We really don't
have it, Gabo.
Still nothing, huh?
Now hit him.
Why me, Gabo?
- Gabo, don't!
- [CROWD CHEERING]
- Hey, don't.
- Just let me hit you
so we can get
this over with.
- Don't do it.
- Come on.
Get ready, okay?
I'll punch you.
- Sorry about this.
- Not too hard, okay?
- Hit him.
- One, two...
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [THUD]
What's going on here?
These three stole
from a woman.
You guys are unbelievable!
[GABO] You still won't fess up?
Bong.
Give me the cannon.
- [TEKLA] Oh, you're in trouble.
- [GABO] Give it to me.
- [OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
- Oh, wait.
There's something in my pocket.
- [TOLITS] Wait.
- [TEKLA] What's that?
- It just appeared there?
- I found this earlier, Gabo.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Good thing you found it.
- I was going to return it.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Miss.
- Is this yours?
- Yes, that's mine.
Go teach them
a lesson, miss.
- Ow!
- That serves you right!
- You thieves!
You can go home now.
We'll take it from here.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
If you show up
here again...
I'll break your faces.
Is that clear?!
Leave!
Get out of here!
- [KICKS LANDING]
- [CROWD CHEERING]
- Run!
- Go, run! Go home!
Everybody, clap!
[CLAPPING, CHEERING]
Django's men
are all the same.
They have the muscle,
but are too lazy to work.
They're not like Gabo
who wants to change for the
better and play fair.
Is it that hard?
As for us, we will work
an honest job.
We won't be like them.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Those cowards!
- [TRAFFIC NOISE]
- [PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Ipe, Ipe.
- What?
See those two chicks
over there?
Where?
I noticed they've been
staring at us for a while.
- Oh, yeah.
- They look like beauty queens.
[LAWIN] Hold on.
- I think they saw us. Hold on.
- Are they looking at us?
- [BONG] Look.
- How can you not see that?
They're not looking at us.
They're looking at Gabo.
Forget him. We saw them first.
Let's approach them.
I like the one in blue.
[IPE]
Fine. Dibs on the other one.
- We'll do it fairly.
- Of course. Come on.
- [BONG, IPE] Hi!
- Miss, miss, miss!
- [BONG] Hello.
- Hi! Hi!
We noticed
you were looking our way.
Is there anything
we can do for you?
Uh...
We're looking for...
cotton fruit.
- Yes, and wax apple.
- Cotton fruit and...
oh, those fruits
are not in season.
But we're selling
something similar
to wax apple and cotton fruit.
- Yeah.
- Oh, let's see it.
[IPE] White and red onions.
These are big.
- Big? Oh, yeah. They're big.
- There.
- [LAWIN] These are really nice.
- But they're not wax apples.
Yes. These are in no way
similar to wax apple.
It's fine, it's fine.
We don't really need it.
But thanks. Thank you, guys.
Hold on. Maybe you want
to buy some fresh onions...
Hey, hey, hey!
What's this?
What's going on here?
Uh, we noticed
these girls staring at us.
And I think...
- I think they like Gabo.
- Yeah, Gabo.
- Who?
- Oh--
[IPE] They like Gabo.
Wow! [CLAPS] Really?
You guys had the nerve,
don't you?
With that cakey makeup, really?
They really think
Gabo will like them?
You girls look like stale fish
sold at the wet market!
Watch your mouth!
You're not that pretty!
- I know I'm pretty, duh.
- Your skin is so pale, girl.
Don't come out here
so arrogant with that chest.
Look at those thighs.
They're as big as a whale.
- Aw! Should I cry?
- Girl, girl, girl.
[TEKLA] What?
- Listen.
- Now she's speaking in English.
- You don't have a future.
- Ugh!
Hey, you! Listen.
You look like
someone from the future!
You're messing
with the wrong person!
Aren't you aware?
You're in my territory.
Hey!
- Oh my god! Oh my god!
- What now?! Come on!
Hey!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[BONG] Hey, stop it!
[PEOPLE SHRIEKING]
[PEOPLE LAUGHING]
Hey!
[TEKLA] Hey!
Hey! Don't flirt with Gabo!
He's mine!
[IPE] They fooled us, Gabo.
We thought they were chicks.
- Damn, they're men! [LAUGHS]
- Frauds!
You guys didn't even help me!
- We knew you could handle it.
- You got that in the bag.
Why did you engage with them?
[STAMMERS]
[IPE] You're such a warfreak.
[TEKLA] Now Gabo's mad at me.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CARS APPROACHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[CAR DOORS OPEN]
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- Aah!
Sir.
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
- It stinks in here.
Or maybe...
it's my breath.
It's not you.
[WATER SPLASHES]
[ISOBEL] My god!
- We're so sorry we're late.
- Isobel!
Pinky! [CHUCKLES]
I'm actually the one
who should apologize
because this is all so sudden.
Ricardo, Isobel,
this is Mr. Nishikawa.
Dude, who are these?
Are they from here?
[RICARDO]
Thank you for your interest.
Hello, I'm Isobel.
This place is huge.
Big. I want to see more.
Of course. Manny.
Boss, is it safe for us
to go in there?
We haven't coordinated
with the district officers.
We'll be fine.
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hon, what's that smell?
It smells like a mix of...
That's the scent of money.
Ooh.
[CHUCKLES]
Well.
Here we are.
Uh, we're thinking that
we will probably put the casino
and the hotel on this side,
right here.
And then,
we're going
to be facing Manila Bay,
and a major, major attraction.
Really? Major, major?
Uh-huh! [CHUCKLES]
(In Japanese) Sounds great.
We'll earn tons of money.
You're right. I can't wait.
Hi, guys. Let's go inside.
Come on.
Sure. [RETCHING] Oh my god.
But it stinks in here.
Oh my gosh.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[BIKE BELL RINGS]
[LOUD MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[ISOBEL] Excuse me.
- Oh!
- Move! Move! Move!
Excuse us. Excuse us.
Hold on, hold on.
After we completely demolish
and level this area...
Come on, come on, come on.
...of the property.
Stop!
Stay right there.
Looking fancy, huh.
You know what,
you don't belong here.
And why are you here anyway?
You never did
an outreach program here.
Why are you here?
Sorry!
We don't need to tell you!
[CROWD GASPS MOCKINGLY]
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh, she's speaking in English.
You think you can intimidate us
with your language?
We can easily
make your nose bleed.
[CROWD CHEERS]
- Exactly!
- [ISOBEL] Guys, please stop!
I can't do this anymore!
My nose might bleed
because this place stinks!
[CROWD GROANS]
What did you just say?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER IN JAPANESE]
We're just checking the area.
We're not here to cause trouble.
Hey, who do you think you are?
And who the hell
are these people?
- Yes!
Hold on. I'm Ricardo Jacinto.
The new owner...
of Ginintuang Lupa.
- [CROWD GASPS]
- Yes!
That's us.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[MUSIC TURNS TENSE]
Hurry!
Hey, what is it?
- What's happening?
- Why are you running?
What's happening?
Why? What's happening?
Juvelyn! Juvelyn!
What's happening?
What's happening?!
The owner
of Ginintuang Lupa is here!
- It's...
- Who?
Ricardo Jacinto!
He wants to demolish our homes!
[ALL] What?!
He can't do that!
This is our home!
- We own this land!
- This land is ours!
Dante, come with me!
Let's go there!
What will happen to us?
Call Betchay!
Betchay! Mameng!
- Hurry!
- Rudy asked you to come.
Where?
I don't know. I'll go there
to see what's happening.
- Why? What's happen--
- Hey, what's this about?
I heard Rudy's name.
What's happening?
I'm not sure.
Why are they running? Hey!
We're not going anywhere.
Period! Go away!
[CROWD CHEERING]
This land is ours!
Am I right, neighbors?
[CROWD CHEERS] Yes!
Oh, please! Please!
Know your place!
Learn to know your place.
[CROWD CLAMORING]
Get out! Get out of here!
Get out!
No way! You can't pass!
Get out of here!
Again, we own this land!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- You should leave instead!
- You can't live here for free!
[RICARDO] We're just taking back
our property!
All of you should be thankful
that we're giving you time
to look for a new place!
Ricardo!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
You bastard!
You're still following me
until here?!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Rudy?
Would you look at that.
To this day
you're still a good for nothing.
You'll pay for what you did
to my family!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
[THUDS]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
- [SMACKING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
Mameng! Betchay!
- Hey, sis!
- What on earth?
- Mameng! Betchay!
- Goodness me.
- Rudy is in a brawl!
- Huh?!
He punched the land lord!
Oh, let's go to him quickly!
Elton, let's go!
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[BLOW LANDS]
- [BAG SMACKS]
- Excuse me! Where's Rudy?
- [BLOW LANDS]
Hey!
- [BAG SMACKING]
- [BETCHAY GRUNTING]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [RICARDO SCREAMS]
[MAMENG] Rudy! Rudy!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [RICARDO SCREAMS]
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
- [ISOBEL] Ricardo!
[BLOWS LANDING]
Rudy, that's enough!
Rudy, come on!
You bastard!
- Rudy!
- Serves you right!
- Go ahead! Get him!
- That's enough!
- Hey!
- Stop it!
Let go of me!
Get out of here! Leave!
- Serves you right!
- Hey!
Mark my words...
I'll make sure that someday
I'll drive all of you
out of here!
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
I'll be back.
We'll be back!
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
- [THUDDING]
[MAN] Get out of here!
Leave!
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
(Speaking in Japanese)
I'm sorry, Mr. Nishikawa!
- Boss...
- I'll leave him to your care.
- [MAN, INAUDIBLE]
- Ricardo, what should we do?!
We should report this
to the police!
- Go do it.
- Okay!
Your days are numbered
here in Ginintuang Lupa!
It's mine! I own this land!
- It's mine!
- Sir, let's leave!
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
- [OBJECTS THUDDING]
You know, it's better if you put
the clearing operations
on hold for now.
I know what I'm doing
and what I should do
with my property!
- [POLICE SIREN WAILING]
- [OBJECTS THUDDING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
You can never us make us
leave this place!
It's not easy
to take over Ginintuang Lupa.
The people there are ferocious.
You'll never tear
our houses down!
[THUDS]
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
- [THUDDING]
[KICK LANDS]
Let us all fight for our rights!
Sir, it's too dangerous.
Let's leave!
- [HITS LANDING]
- It's Gabo!
- I finally caught you!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- Move out of the way!
[GUNSHOT]